isnetworld.com 2018-09-14

# Privacy Policy | ISN

Thank you for visiting ISNetworld. This ISN Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you of the policies and procedures that will apply to the collection, security, use, and disclosure of information by ISN Software Corporation, a Delaware corporation, and its subsidiaries (“ISN,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) in connection with our business.

Section 1.  About ISNetworld.

ISN owns and operates an online contractor-management platform called (“ISNetworld”). Through ISNetworld, we collect health and safety, procurement, quality, regulatory and similar information from ISNetworld-subscribing contractor customers (“ISNetworld Contractors”), ISNetworld data providers (“Data Providers”) and other public and private third-party sources (such as governmental databases), in order for that information to be shared by the ISNetworld Contractors with certain ISNetworld-subscribing hiring clients (“Hiring Clients”) for use in their contractor and supplier due-diligence and management processes and in connection with other services that we may offer from time to time (collectively, our “Services”). 

Section 2.  How ISN Collects, Uses, and Shares Information.

This section describes in more detail how we collect, use, and share different types of information.

A. ISNetworld Content.

Our Services allow ISNetworld Contractors, ISNetworld Data Providers and Hiring Clients to upload or enter content into ISNetworld (“ISNetworld Content”) to be stored and shared with other ISNetworld users. In general, and except as required by law, we will process ISNetworld Content only as required in order for us to provide our Services to Hiring Clients and ISNetworld Contractors (please see our standard User Agreements for additional information regarding our Services) or otherwise in accordance with consent or the reasonable written instructions of the ISNetworld Contractor, ISNetworld Data Provider, or Hiring Client who entered the ISNetworld Content into ISNetworld. In certain instances we may be required to disclose ISNetworld Content to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or to other third parties, in each case to comply with legal, regulatory, or national security obligations or requests.

As part of our Services, we assemble and retain data from ISNetworld Content for the purposes of benchmarking and providing comparative and other generalized analyses and reports (“Benchmarking”). Any data we report from Benchmarking is aggregated and anonymized.

It is important to us that ISNetworld Content remains accurate, complete, and up-to-date. As we rely on Hiring Clients, ISNetworld Contractors and ISNetworld Data Providers for ISNetworld Content, we take steps to ensure these parties understand the importance of keeping the information they maintain and share through ISNetworld as accurate and current as possible. However, each Hiring Client, ISNetworld Contractor, and ISNetworld Data Provider is ultimately responsible for the accuracy and completeness of the ISNetworld Content that it provides to us.

B. Cookies.

We collect certain information automatically from visitors to our website, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, access times, browser types, device types, domain names, durations of visit, and referring URLs, through the use of “cookies.” A cookie is a small piece of text sent to a browser by a website accessed through the browser. Cookies help websites remember information about visitors. We use information from cookies and share it with other organizations with which we have a commercial relationship to measure the use of our website, to improve the functionality and content of our website and our Services, and to facilitate usage by visitors. We do not use cookies to collect information about individual user behavior on our website, and, unless a visitor informs us (e.g., by registering for an event or sending us correspondence from the website), we will not know the specific identity of a visitor from the data we collect from cookies.

Visitors can reset their browsers either to notify them when they receive cookies or to refuse to accept cookies. However, by refusing to accept cookies from our website, a visitor may not be able to use some of the features available on our website or through our Services.

C. Personal Information.

This subsection details how we collect, use, and disclose Personal Information (as defined below). For purposes of this subsection, (i) “Personal Information” means individually-identifiable information that, alone or when in combination with other information, may be used to identify, contact, or locate a specific person, such as a name, address, phone number, username, or email address; and (ii) “you” or “your” refers to the individual who is the subject of the relevant Personal Information, regardless of whether that individual is an ISNetworld subscriber.

(i) Content Personal Information.

We do not control the type or accuracy of the ISNetworld Content that ISNetworld Contractors, ISNetworld Data Providers, and Hiring Clients provide to us, which may include Personal Information (“Content Personal Information”). Most of the ISNetworld Content, including Content Personal Information, consists of information that ISNetworld Contractors and ISNetworld Data Providers provide to us in response to requests from Hiring Clients. For example, if you work for an ISNetworld Contractor, a Hiring Client for whom your employer works might request certain information about you, including your name, occupation, contact information, training and work-related history, and other information relevant to your work qualifications, be entered into ISNetworld for the Hiring Client to view as part of its due diligence processes. Each ISNetworld Contractor, ISNetworld Data Provider, and Hiring Client is responsible for managing the Content Personal Information it enters into ISNetworld and for taking all measures necessary to comply with applicable privacy laws to ensure we may lawfully process, use, and disclose such Content Personal Information to provide our Services. 

To the extent applicable privacy laws require your consent to be obtained prior to or during the course of our processing any Content Personal Information about you, the ISNetworld Contractor, ISNetworld Data Provider, or Hiring Client who entered your Content Personal Information into ISNetworld is responsible for obtaining your consent to both (i) us processing your Content Personal Information for purposes of providing our Services, and (ii) if you reside outside of the United States, us transferring your Content Personal Information to the United States for our processing.

If any Content Personal Information about you has been provided without your consent or is incorrect, you should first ask your employer or principal to take the necessary steps to have it removed from or corrected in ISNetworld.

(ii) Information about ISNetworld Users.

Each Hiring Client, ISNetworld Contractor, and ISNetworld Data Provider will have at least one, and sometimes many, individuals registered as users of its ISNetworld account. We collect information, including Personal Information, when individuals register as users of an ISNetworld account and thereafter when they access our Services (“User Personal Information”). For example, if you are requesting to be set up as a user of a Hiring Client’s account, we will ask you to provide us your name, email address, the name of your employer, and other information we may need in order to activate and maintain your user account.

We may use your User Personal Information to contact you from time to time in connection with our Services, such as to address any issues or complaints related to your use of ISNetworld, provide you with information about ISNetworld or our Services, verify your identity or credentials, provide any required legal notices to you, or notify you if we believe your use of our Services violates any of our terms or policies.

(iii) Communications with ISN.

We collect information when we receive communications from ISNetworld users and third parties. The information we collect from communications includes Personal Information received via emails, telephone calls, postal mails, online chats, and inquiries through our website (“Communicated Personal Information”).

We may use your Communicated Personal Information to respond to you, provide you with information about ISNetworld or our Services, provide any required legal notices to you, or address any issues related to your communications.

(iv) International Privacy Issues.

ISNetworld and our Services are primarily operated and managed within the United States. Accordingly, if you reside or are located outside of the United States, your Personal Information may be transferred outside of the country where you reside or are located, including to countries whose laws do not provide the same level of protection for your Personal Information as the laws of your home country. Please see the Global Operations page on our website for the jurisdictions where we operate. However, we are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of Personal Information when it is transferred and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that, in the event we transfer your Personal Information to a location outside of your home country, your Personal Information is protected and our practices and procedures comply with all relevant privacy laws.

Certain jurisdictions may require specific privacy practices, which may be addressed in jurisdiction-specific policies accessible from our homepage (for example, see our Privacy Shield Policy and our Australian Privacy Principles Policy).

(v) Obtaining Access to Your Personal Information.

Upon your written request, and subject to certain exceptions, we will inform you of the existence, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information and will give you access to that information.

You have the right to request access to and correction of any of your Personal Information that we hold. You should first ask your employer or principal to obtain such access or to take the necessary steps to have your Personal Information removed from or corrected in ISNetworld; however, you may contact us at any time as provided in _Section 5_ below to request assistance in accessing your Personal Information. If access to your Personal Information is denied, we will notify you in writing, give reasons for the denial, and inform you of the recourses open to you. If access is granted, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to review your Personal Information. Your Personal Information will be provided to you in an understandable form within a reasonable time, generally within 30 days. ISN may extend such 30 day period by up to an additional 30 days if meeting the time limit would unreasonably interfere with the activities of ISN or the time required to undertake any consultations necessary to respond to your request would make the time limit impracticable to meet. You will be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of your Personal Information and have it amended as appropriate.

(vi) Retention.

In general, ISN retains information in order to meet business, tax, legal, regulatory and archival requirements. We retain the personal information we collect for so long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the data was collected, to perform our Services and other contractual and legal obligations, and for any applicable statute of limitations periods for the purposes of bringing and defending claims.

Section 3.  Disclosures to Affiliates and Service Providers.

We disclose information we collect to our related corporate affiliates and service providers who assist us in providing the Services and are bound by relevant confidentiality requirements.

Section 4.  Safeguarding Measures and Transfer of Information Overseas.

We are committed to protecting the security of the information we collect. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect such information from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure and from misuse, interference and loss. We collect and store information electronically. All such information is stored in secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities located in the United States. We regularly monitor and update our security procedures to ensure we have industry-standard or better measures in place at all times to protect against unintended disclosures or use of the information we collect.

Section 5.  Contact Information.

We welcome any questions or comments you might have about our Services and the information provided in this Privacy Policy. We recommend employees and subcontractors of ISNetworld Contractors and Hiring Clients raise their questions, requests or complaints with the ISNetworld Contractor or Hiring Client for whom they work at first instance. Questions, requests or complaints received directly by ISNetworld in the first instance may be referred to the relevant ISNetworld Contractor or Hiring Client (or both).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our Services, any problems or complaints about how we have collected, used, stored, handled and/or disclosed information, or wish to make a request to access, erase, or correct any information, please contact us by telephone or email as follows:

Telephone: 1-800-976-1303   
Email: [info@ISN.com](mailto:info@isn.com)

Section 6.  Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, such as to account for new laws and technologies, changes to our Services, and for other reasonable purposes. In the event we amend this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website ([www.ISNetworld.com](https://www.isnetworld.com/)).
